question_data = [
    {"category": "Science & Nature",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia is the irrational fear of long words.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The planet Mars has two moons orbiting it.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Steel is an alloy of Iron and Carbon.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "A defibrillator is used to start up a heartbeat once a heart has stopped beating.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Shrimp can swim backwards.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Anatomy considers the forms of macroscopic structures such as organs and organ systems.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Scientists accidentally killed the once known world&#039;s oldest living creature, a mollusc, "
                 "known to be aged as 507 years old.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the periodic table, Potassium&#039;s symbol is the letter K.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Sugar contains fat.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Tachycardia&quot; or &quot;Tachyarrhythmia&quot; "
                 "refers to a resting heart-rate near or over 100 BPM.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
